下午好  欧森小姐
Good afternoon, Miss Ocean.
你好
Hi.
你应该知道  假释是特殊待遇
As you know, parole is a privilege.
假释的限制条件之一
And one of the restrictions on any parolee,
就是避免与
is to avoid the company
任何有犯罪记录的人共处
of any person who has a criminal record of any kind.
那基本排除了你的大多数家人
That would include most of your extended family.
我并不以此为豪
Yeah, that's obviously not something I'm proud of.
这对你来说是不可能完成的挑战吗
Would this pose an impossible challenge for you?
不  不
No. No.
我不想要那种生活  我从来不想要那种生活
I don't want that life. I never wanted that life.
我哥哥
My brother, um...
愿他安息
May he rest in peace,
是个罪犯
was a criminal.
我爱他
I loved him,
但他是个诈骗犯
but he was a conman.
那是他骨子里的基因
It was in his blood.
你骨子里没有吗  没有
And it's not in your blood?  No.
没有  长官
No, sir.
我爱错了人
I fell for the wrong person.
那是个错误
It was a mistake.
但还是发生了
But it happened.
如果我能出狱  我会...
And if I were to be released, I would, um...
抱歉
Sorry.
就算说出来也...
Wow, just saying that...
如果我能出狱
If I were to be released,
我只想过上简单的生活
I would just want the simple life.
我只想找个工作
I just wanna hold down a job,
结交点朋友
make some friends,
下班后去散散步  呼吸新鲜空气
go for a walk after work in the fresh air
养活自己
and pay my bills.
简单的生活
Simple life?
演得不错
Nice one.
你听说了吗  还有谁不知道
Heard about that?  Who didn't?
我花了五年排练呢
I had five years to rehearse it.
你的东西  谢谢
Here's your stuff.  Thank you.
表不错
Nice watch.
丹尼
是我哥哥的  传给你的吗
It's my brother's.  Left it to you?
是我偷的
I stole it.
没关系  迪娜  他也是偷来的
It's fine, Dina. He stole it, too.
下周还是照常送一批货
So we're still gonna get a regular shipment next week.
你拿走你那份  再多拿几盒
You take your cut, plus a few extra cartons, okay?
我要你卖了  不是全抽了
I want you to trade 'em, not smoke 'em.
你打算去哪里
So where you going?
我有45块呢  迪娜
Well, I have 45 bucks, Dina.
想去哪里都行
I can go anywhere I want.
尼克斯女子监狱
新泽西劳教所
片名    瞒天过海：美人计（八罗汉）
波道夫·古德曼
你好  我想退掉这些
Hi, I'd like to return these.
好的  你有收据吗
Oh, of course. Do you have your receipt?
没有  但都没拆封过  没碰过
No, but they're unopened. They haven't been touched.
我真的需要你的收据
I really need your receipt.
这些都是密封的  全新的
They are sealed. They are brand new.
你带了当时使用的信用卡吗
Do you have the credit card that you used?
太荒谬了  我上周才买的
This is ridiculous! I bought these last week.
女士  你可以去六楼的客户服务中心
Ma'am, you can try client services on the sixth floor.
你知道吗  算了  我不退了
You know what? Never mind. I'll just keep 'em.
上帝啊
Jesus.
至少能给我一个袋子吧
Can I at least get a bag?
当然了
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好  退2814号房  盖瑞·兰德尔
Hi. I'm checking out of room 2814. Gary Randall.
请问您住得开心吗  很好
Did you have a pleasant stay?  Terrific.
我叫莫妮卡
My name is Monica.
还有什么需要我为您效劳的吗
Is there anything else I can do for you?
是否需要安排接送
Or arrange transportation?
我们都安排好了
I think we're all set.
你好  我是兰德尔太太
Hi, this is Mrs. Randall.
我们刚退了2814号房
We just checked out of room 2814.
我想找莫妮卡
May I speak with Monica, please?
是我  你好  莫妮卡
This is she.  Hi, Monica.
你好  你好
Hi.  Hi.
我们刚发现我们的飞机取消了
Uh, we just found out our flight was canceled.
不  我知道  我知道
Oh, no!  I know, I know.
我们不想住在
And instead of staying
机场边的破旅店里
in some horrible airport hotel,
所以我们想能不能
we were hoping that maybe
要回我们原来的房间
we could get our original room back?
当然了  你们可以继续订那间房
Yeah, we can give you that same room back.
那真是太好了  太感谢你了
That would be amazing! Thank you so much!
我们准备先去吃点东西
Um, we're just gonna go grab a bite.
能找人先去打扫吗
Would it be possible to get the maid in there now?
当然了
Yes, absolutely.
太好了  真的很感谢
Perfect. We really appreciate it.
没问题
It's not a problem.
太感谢了  待会见
Thank you so much. We'll see you soon.
你好
Hi.
很抱歉  你能等会儿再来打扫吗
I'm so sorry. Can you finish up later?
我得好好休息一下
I just have to get off my feet.
当然了  太感谢你了
Of course.  Thank you so much.
祝您愉快  你也是
Have a great day.  You, too!
再见
Byebye.
结果他没搬进来
And he did not move in!
他想要回他的钱
And he wants his money back.
他还真的拿回了他的钱
And he gets his money back.
如果你说没拿  那就能说明你没有拿钱吗
If you said no, does that mean you didn't take the money?
你手上是几号箱
What crate are you on?
15.
听着
Listen.
你觉得我喜欢你吗  我相信你吗
You think I like you? You think I believe you?
你觉得我相信你说的话吗
You think I trust anything that you're saying?
答案是绝对不可能
The answer is absolutely not.
伙计们  9点30分了
Guys, it's 9:30.
太多了  太多了
It's too much. It's too much.
应该是离瓶盖三指
It's three fingers from the top.
不是一指  三指
Not one, it's three.
这是重播  爱普莉尔
It's a rerun, April.
她睡了自己的表哥  撞了车
She slept with her cousin, crashed the car.
宝宝不是他的
The baby's not his.
尝起来什么味
What's that taste like?
伏特加
Vodka.
伏特加  没错  但我不想要伏特加
Vodka. Exactly. But I don't want vodka.
我想要伏特加加水
I want vodka and water.
你知道为什么吗  你说
And do you wanna know why?  Uh, sure.
因为你喝醉了时  这尝起来就像伏特加
'Cause when you're drunk, it tastes like vodka.
对  对
Right.  Right.
我不在乎
I don't care!
那该死的公墓在哪里  晚上12点吗
我也想你
Oh, missed you, too.
丹尼·欧森
你最好在里面
You better be in there.
我知道你在  鲁本
I know you're there, Reuben.
你可以出来了
You can come on out.
我只是在哀悼
I was just paying my respects.
在角落里吗
From around the corner?
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
他们觉得找我来和你说最好
They thought I'd be the best one to talk to you.
我要走了
Hmm. Gotta go.
他不想你这么做  黛布拉
He didn't want you to do this, Deborah.
做什么
Do what?
就是他不愿意告诉我们的你在做的事
Whatever it is he wouldn't tell us you're gonna do.
听着  黛布
Look, Deb.
有时候  你只要知道能够成功
Sometimes, just knowing the job will work
就已经够满足了
is satisfaction enough.
你不用非得动手
You don't actually gotta do it.
他还说了什么
What else did he say?
他说真是太天才了  好吧
He said it was brilliant.  Oh, okay.
还有你很可能会回监狱
And that you would probably end up back in prison.
我不会回监狱的
I'm not gonna end up back in prison.
好吗
Okay?
我要走了
I gotta go.
小心点
Be careful.
你看上去很帅
You're looking sharp.
冷静点
Take it easy.
刚蹲过监狱呢
Been in the slammer.
我还以为你换号码了
Oh, I just thought you changed your number.
搞到信贷额度了吗
Did you get the credit line?
还没有  为什么
Not yet.  Why not?
因为我不知道是用来干什么的
Because I don't know what it's for.
天啊
Oh, my God!
别这样
Don't do that.
哪样
Do what?
那就是我"我蹲了五年监狱
That would be my "I've just been in jail for five years,
结果我搭档让我失望了"的表情
"And my partner lets me down" Face.
我还不是你的搭档
Hey, I'm not your partner. Yet.
这儿真不错
This is nice.
钢丝围栏   带刺铁丝网
Chainlink, barb wire.
给你带了点东西
Brought you something.
我可以换点你偷来的东西吗
Can I exchange something you stole?
如果你对偷东西有意见
Well, if you're gonna have a problem with stealing,
你可能不会喜欢我们接下来要说的事
you're not gonna like the rest of this conversation.
怎么  我们得去商店偷东西吗  也许
What, we're gonna shoplift?  Maybe.
不  你总是这样
No. See, this is what you do.
你让我来猜  然后我就会感兴趣
You make me guess and then, I'm interested.
好吧  你认为因为
Okay.  And then you think because
我感兴趣  我就会想干
I'm interested, that I wanna do it.
你不想干你感兴趣的事吗
Don't you wanna do things you're interested in?
我对脑部手术有兴趣
I'm interested in brain surgery.
我们都知道那是不可能的
Well, we know that's not gonna happen.
随便了  你不想告诉我...
Whatever. You don't wanna tell me...
珠宝
It's jewels.
炫目  完美  又大又闪的
Spectacular, great, big, blingy,
丽斯·泰勒珠宝
big old Liz Taylor jewels,
锁在一个在地下50英尺的保险箱中
that are locked in a vault 50 feet underground.
我们怎么把它们从保险箱中拿出来
How do we get them out of the vault?
他们会乖乖送上门
They're gonna bring 'em to us.
该死
Oh, bugger!
这地方不错
Nice place.
开暖气试试
Try heating it.
你的房间在楼上
There's a room for you upstairs.
你的东西也在楼上
Your stuff's upstairs, too.
我借了点东西
You know, I borrowed some shit.
我还以为你永远都用不上了呢
Figured you weren't using it.
克劳德·贝克画廊
这是你的画廊吗
So, is this your gallery?
对  其中之一
Yeah, one of them.
其他的在哪里
Where are the others?
伦敦的那家正准备开业
Well, I'm opening one in London.
准备在东京再开一家
Got plans for another one in Tokyo.
我们也在考虑洛杉矶
We're talking about LA,
但我不确定能不能成
but I'm not sure that makes sense.
那里有点缺乏创意
It's all a bit derivative out there, you know?
所以其实现在只有这一家
So this is the only one that exists?
实体上是这样
Well... Physically.
抱歉失陪一下
Excuse me one second.
抱歉  抱歉
Sorry. Sorry.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我本来想给你打电话的
I was meaning to call you.
天啊  看到你真好  你看上去...
Jesus, it's great to see you. You look...
进过监狱吗
Recently incarcerated?
很美  你看上去很美
Wonderful. You look wonderful.
你知道什么是刺刀吗
Do you know what a shiv is?
行了  住手  住手
Okay, stop. Just stop.
多么帅气的脸
Oh, such a nice face.
内心深处
You know, inside,
你就是一个小姑娘
you're what we call a pretty girl.
我要报警了  好的
I'll call the police.  Okay.
你知道我们怎么对待告密者吗
Do you know what we do with snitches?
他看到你了  对
He saw you?  Oh, yeah.
你为什么要做这种事
Why would you do something like that?
做个了结
Closure?
胡扯
Bullshit!
上帝啊
Jesus!
那你...
So did you...
没有
No.
只要了一个小纽扣
Just a little button.
一开始我考虑的是银行  因为...
So at first, I thought banks. 'Cause you know...
钱都存在那里嘛
That's where they have money?
没错  但是那有点无聊
Exactly. But that's kind of boring.
于是我想抢十家银行
So then I thought ten banks.
然后我意识到那可能
Then I realized that would be maybe
只有不理智的人才会...
coming from an angry place so...
还好你意识到了
Good you realized that.
是的  然后我就没法安静思考了
Yes. Then I couldn't even hear myself think.
一个号子里住五个女人呢
You know, five women in one cell.
于是我就想办法进了禁闭室
So I got myself thrown in solitary
在那个安静的环境下
for a little peace and quiet,
终于想出了一个主意
and that's where I finally came up with it.
权杖与宝珠
欧洲皇权的历史进程
这毕竟还是个博物馆  所以呢
It's still a museum.  So?
所以这不像去抢个酒水商店
So, it's not like robbing a liquor store.
抱歉  我不会说乌克兰语
I'm sorry, I don't speak Ukrainian.
我说  "我们不抢博物馆"
I said, "We're not robbing a museum."
我们要抢
We're robbing someone...
博物馆里的人
In a museum.
嗯  你提过了
Yeah, you mentioned.
听着
Look.
就算有成功的可能...  就是有可能
Even if this was possible...  It is possible.
就算有可能  我们还需要
Even if it was, we'd need, like,
20多个人和五十万资金
20 people and half a million dollars.
七
Seven.
七百万吗
Seven million?
七个人和两万
Seven people and 20 grand.
你为什么非要这么做
Why do you need to do this?
因为这是我擅长的
Because it's what I'm good at.
好吧
Uh, yeah.
你知道吗
You know what?
我预想了一千多次
I have run this thing a thousand times.
每次发展到被抓  我就会做改进
Every time I got caught, I fixed it.
三年了  我再也没被抓过
And in three years, I wasn't getting caught anymore.
在我得到假释时  一切在我脑中已经宛如时钟般精确
By the time I was paroled, it was running like clockwork.
完美
Perfectly.
每一步  你都跟我在一起
And you were there with me, every step of the way.
亲爱的  你是在向我求婚吗
Oh, honey, is this a proposal?
宝贝  我还没拿到钻石呢
Baby, I don't have a diamond yet.
拜托  你真的想下半辈子
Come on. Do you really wanna spend the rest
都靠给伏特加掺水度日吗
of your life watering down well vodka?
那可真是暴殄天物
Because it's really kind of a waste.
来一口
Come on. Take a bite.
就一口
Just take a bite.
你真的很烦人  张嘴
You're really irritating.  Open.
味道不错
That's good.
很不错
Very good.
大都会艺术博物馆年度展记者招待会
每年他们都会举办
So each year they host
全世界最大的派对
the biggest party in the world.
他们经常会请一名巨星来主持
And they always get a huge celebrity to host.
今年是达芙妮·克卢格
This year, it's Daphne Kluger.
没错  但她不是我们的目标
Yeah. But she's not our mark.
那谁是目标
So who's the mark?
好了  谁想第一个提问
All right, who wants to go first?
请提问
Yes.
你知道你穿谁的设计吗
Do you know who you're wearing?
拉珀拉  黑色的[内衣]
La Perla. It's black.
不  我是指谁给你造型
No, I mean who's dressing you?
我现在真的还不知道
I don't really know yet.
设计师
The designer.
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
一旦我知道了
But as soon as I do,
我就第一个告诉你
you'll be the very first person that I tell.
下一个问题
Uh, next question?
好了  我们需要一个设计师
All right, we need a designer.
没错
Exactly!
我们有很多目标
Now a lot of these we could target.
但是安娜不会同意的
But Anna won't approve them,
而一切都得安娜同意才行
and Anna has to approve everything.
我知道
I know.
有不少牌子没那么硬的选择
There's a few lessestablished choices,
但是他们可不会给我们带来什么优势
but they're not gonna give us the juice we need.
那么
So...
罗斯·威尔  我为什么知道这个名字
Rose Weil. Why do I know that name?
她很有名  在九十年代
Well, she was big, in the '90s.
天啊  那种爱德华式衣领和袖边
Oh, God, all the Edwardian collars and the ruffles.
很滑稽  但是安娜还是喜欢她
Travesty. But Anna still likes her.
她们每年都在肯特一起过复活节
They do Easter together every year in Kent.
英国人吗  爱尔兰人
Brits?  Irish.
而且她还欠了五百万的税
And she owes the IRS $5 million.
很糟糕
It's bad.
她的财产都被扣押了
There's a lien on her assets,
纽约
他们扣押了她的护照
they've impounded her passport.
银行没收了她的房子
The bank seized her townhouse.
她听起来很棒
She sounds amazing.
没错
Yeah.
我觉得我们很走运
I think we got lucky.
她赌上了一切
She gambled everything on this.
这可是一条看不到前景的路
This is a flight to nowhere without any peanuts.
自己筹钱  在奥马哈银行借贷
Selffinanced. Credit from an Omaha bank.
那边的那些人
Those guys over there?
是为数不多愿意借钱给她的人
The only ones who'll still loan her money.
他们看上去有点担心
They look a little worried.
谁能怪他们呢  这简直是一团糟
Yeah, who can blame them? This is a train wreck.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你们是谁
Who are you?
你的粉丝
Big fans.
狂热粉丝
Very big.
刚刚...  真是
That was...  Just...
太美了
Gorgeous.
不  不是的
No, it wasn't.
那是一场灾难
It was a disaster.
我觉得你对你自己太苛刻了
I think you're being kind of hard on yourself.
很苛刻
Very.
你们看过这个了吗
Did you read this?
是一个博主写的
It's by a blogger.
"罗斯·威尔
"Rose Weil.
她的新时装系列就像逛了一圈
"Her new collection is like taking a tour
你奶奶的衣橱
of your grandmother's closet.
又过时  又陈旧
"Just as dated, and just as musty.
爱斯基摩人会把老年人都赶到浮冰上
"The Eskimo shove their elders out on an ice floe.
没别的意思"
"Just saying."
太残忍了
That's very cruel.
但这并不说明就是那样的
But it doesn't make it true.
我怎么会变成这样
How did I get here?
你两年花光了一千八百万
You spent $18 million in two years
还在塞纳河上买了两条船屋
and had two houseboats on the Seine.
我老了
I'm old.
你不老
Hey, you're not old.
我老了  我要进监狱了
I'm old, and I'm going to prison.
我会变得很穷很穷
Then I'm going to be really, really poor.
不一定
Not necessarily.
如果我们能让这一切都消失
What if we could make all this go away?
还能拿回你的护照呢
Even get your passport back.
怎么做
How?
为达芙妮·克卢格设计大都会晚宴的扮相
Dress Daphne Kluger for the Met Ball.
你疯了吗
Are you mad?
不  等等
No, hang on a minute.
你们是记者吗
Are you journalists?
当然不是  上帝啊  不是
Absolutely not.  God, no.
她看上去有点紧绷  有可能
Hmm. She seems sort of tense.  Can be.
好身材  好胸  特征明显
Good body. Good boobs. Huge features.
一双小鹿眼
Eyes like Bambi.
没错  她能驾驭很多服装
Yeah. She can take quite a lot.
也许我们能给她...也许...
Maybe we could give her... Maybe...
也许我们能给她这个
Maybe we could give her this.
天啊  不行  不够时尚  我们能用更好的
God, no. Not chic. We can do better than that.
它的名字叫杜桑
It's called the Toussaint.
以贞·杜桑命名
Named for Jeanne Toussaint,
1933年到1968年卡蒂亚的珠宝总监
Cartier's director of jewelry from '33 to '68.
镶有超过六磅重的钻石
It's over six pounds of diamonds.
好吧
Right.
她死后  他们将它卖回给卡蒂亚
After she died, they sold it back to Cartier,
后来就一直藏在他们的保险库中
and they've kept it in their vault ever since.
他们从来没拿出来过
They've never let it out.
那我们要怎么拿出来
So then, how are we gonna get it out?
他们也许会为她拿出来
Well, they might let it out for her.
今年晚宴的主题
The theme of this year's ball
是欧洲皇室
is European royalty...
王冠宝石是其特征元素
...of which the crown jewels are a featured element.
所以如果你坚持要
So, if you were to insist on the Toussaint
达芙妮·克卢格戴杜桑
on behalf of Daphne Kluger...
肯定很值钱
Must be worth quite a lot.
没错
Yeah.
都是俄罗斯人  他们是黑客
These are all Russians.  They're hackers.
有不是俄罗斯人的黑客吗
Are there no hackers who aren't Russian?
没有  俄罗斯人没有几个不是黑客的
No, there's barely any Russians who aren't hackers.
拜托  继续找吧  好
Just keep looking, please.  Sure.
这不是无暇的
这是块好石头  你怎么回事
我是在这里工作的  别骗我
这颗钻石最多只有K级
这是H级
你疯了吗  这是尿黄色
你怎么这么粗俗  如果你父亲还活着
那你自己评级吧
所以你找不到老公
就像你姐姐
好吧
Okay.
丹尼的事我很遗憾
Sorry about Danny.
你爸爸的事我很遗憾
Sorry about your pops.
你来这里干什么
So, what are you doing here?
我可能有事找你
I might have something for you.
一个活
A job.
你想在店里出点货吗
You wanna run some stuff through the store?
不用  谢谢
No, thank you.
没这么简单
A little more than that.
你要花多久
How long would it take you
能用已经切割好的原石
to make seven pieces of jewelry,
做七件首饰
if the stones were already cut?
可能要五六小时
Probably five or six hours.
如果我告诉你  你不用再和你妈妈
How long if I told you you didn't have to
住在一起了呢
live with your mother anymore?
再快点
Less.
我再也不坐F线了
I'm never taking the Ftrain again.
她进去了
She's in.
她进哪里了
She is in where?
你说得就是这些吗  一堆花瓶
This what you talking about? Bunch of vases.
没错  那是埃及翅膀
Yeah, that's the Egyptian wing.
她黑进大都会了
She's in the Met?
监控摄像头
Security cameras.
有很多呢
There's a lot of 'em.
我叫黛比
My name's Debbie.
九球  你的真名是什么
Nine Ball.  What's your real name?
八球
Eight Ball.
你在这里得用真名
We use real names around here.
我能和你谈谈吗
Could I talk to you for a minute?
我要你给我找个黑客
I asked you to get me a hacker.
她是东海岸最棒的黑客之一
She is one of the best hackers on the East Coast.
我很荣幸  她还有别的客户
Oh, I'm honored...  She has other clients.
他们也不知道她的真名
They don't know her real name either.
不好意思  "其他客户"
I'm sorry, "Other clients"?
现在还有吗  是的
Now?  Yeah.
你有告诉她能分到多少钱吗
Did you tell her what her cut was?
当然了  然后呢
Of course.  And?
看  她在抽烟
Look. She's smoking!
九球
So, Nine Ball.
我要叫你九球  九...
Uh, do I call you Nine Ball? Nine...
或者球手
Or Baller.
球手  好吧
Baller? Okay. Okay.
你知道你的足迹一团糟吧
You know your footprint is a disaster, right?
抱歉  什么  你的足迹
I'm sorry, what?  Your footprint.
我的足迹  没错  女士
My footprint?  Yes, ma'am.
如果你想偷东西
If you're planning to steal shit,
你可得清理干净
you definitely got to clean this up,
现在  我的小妹妹都能黑了你们
'cause right now, my little sister could hack you.
好吧  因为我们有个人...
Oh, right. 'Cause we had this guy...
明白了
Gotcha.
我们会清理的
We'll clean that up.
我能问问我们要去哪里吗  待会就知道了
Can I ask where we're going?  You'll see in a minute.
现在  我们要去见
Right, we're going to meet
多丽丝·克卢格  达芙妮
Doris Kluger...  Daphne.
达芙妮  比她更著名的人
Daphne.  Someone even more famous.
会让达芙妮·克卢格嫉妒的人
Someone who makes Daphne Kluger jealous.
嫉妒
Jealous?
过一会  我们会站起来离开
In a minute, we're gonna stand up.
她会坐下来
She's gonna sit down.
你会认出她  淡定点
You'll recognize her. Just be cool.
高冷  但要和善
Aloof.  But kind.
但不能太和善  对
But not too kind.  Yeah.
你在出汗
You're sweating.
对  我很会出汗  别出
Yeah, look, I sweat.  Don't.
她的左手有一个纹身
On her left hand is a tattoo.
我要你握住它  称赞它
I want you to take it, admire it,
要进行身体接触  然后我们会拍下来
but make physical contact, and that's when we'll get it.
它  什么它
"It"? What's "It"?
我知道你
Oh, I know you!
我知道你  我见过你  我见过你很多次
Yes, I know you. I've seen you. I've seen you in things.
没错
Yeah.
不  你很棒  谢谢
No, you're good.  Oh, thank you.
你真的很棒  谢谢
You're really good. Yeah.  Thank you.
我只是很想和你说"谢谢"
Well, I just really wanted to say, "Thank you."
谢谢
Thank you?
帮助我们的猫咪救援项目
For helping us with the feline rescue project.
佩内洛佩·斯特恩
Penelope Stern?
她年纪够参加大都会晚会了吗
Is she even old enough to go to the Met Ball?
显然可以
Apparently.
谁在乎谁给她造型
Who cares who's dressing her anyway?
我觉得第六版在乎
Uh, I think Page Six.
大都会舞会搭档
我没见过罗斯·威尔  你说我和所有人都见过了
I never met with Rose Weil. You said I met with everybody.
你说她是个老古董  我是说老标杆
You said she was a relic.  I meant iconic.
你要我安排一次见面吗
Do you want me to set up a meeting?
当然了  好的
Yes!  Okay.
我昨晚看了她的一部电影
I watched one of her films last night.
她其实还真的挺不错
She's actually really good.
不管怎么样  不要奉承她
Whatever you do, don't fawn.
别理她
Just ignore her.
冷漠能催生欲望
Indifference, it's an aphrodisiac.
避免眼神接触
Very little eye contact.
罗斯
Rose.
达芙妮·克卢格女士  终于见面了
Daphne. Miss Kluger.  Finally.
谢谢你愿意在最后时刻见我
So, thank you so much for meeting me so last minute.
我很崇拜你  我有很多你的作品
I am such an admirer of yours. I have so many of your pieces.
真的吗  没错
Really?  Yeah.
找人...可真是不简单
So, this search... It has not been easy.
我们看了这么多人
And everything we've seen,
他们都很不错
you know, it's been great.
但是都疲劳了
But it's been tired
你看上去很不一样
and you just seem different.
你好像不在意外界评价
You know, like you're immune to judgment.
仿佛完全超脱了
Like you're above all that.
抱歉  怎么回事
I'm sorry, what?
你怎么回事
What is going on?
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
你说什么
Um, what were you saying?
我想雇你做我大都会晚会的设计师
I'm trying to hire you for the Met Ball.
太好了  谢谢你  我很荣幸
Great. Thank you. My honor.
受宠若惊
Flattered.
先别说得太早  半路杀出达芙妮
你看到就知道了
Wait till you see.
这姑娘有一双我所见过最妙的手
This girl has some of the best hands I've ever seen.
这人正常吗
Is this one sane?
完全正常
Hundred percent.
好了  玩法是这样的
All right, here's how we're playing.
红色就有钱
Red is money, okay?
真的吗  三牌赌一张
Really? Threecard Monte?
跟着皇后  实现梦想
Follow the Queen, live your dream.
不过你可别睡着了  别睡着了
But don't sleep. Don't sleep.
因为她可能会消失  看到了吗
'Cause she might disappear, you saw that?
不见了吧
It's lit, right?
但她会回来  她喜欢你
She came back, though. She likes you.
好了  开始吧  跟着皇后
All right, let's hit it. And we're following the Queen.
我们跟着皇后
And we're following the Queen.
只能选她了吗
Is this our only choice?
小偷的营业额可不是小数
The turnover in pickpockets is huge.
她在哪里  这贱人在哪里
Where she at? Where that bitch at?
她在哪里
Where she at?
那个
That one.
百分百肯定就是那张了吗
Wanna call a lifeline on that one?
不  那张
No. That one.
好了  那是我的了
All right. That one is mine.
好了  别难过
Come on, there's no hard feelings.
你真的很厉害  懂我意思吗
And you're a real one, you know? You know what I mean?
欢迎你随时回来
Yeah, come back any time.
不赖  我就说吧
Not bad.  Yeah. I thought so.
火鸡和伏洛干酪
Turkey and provolone, please.
所以  我要偷一条项链
So, I'm lifting one necklace.
一条很不错的项链
It's a very nice necklace.
生菜和番茄
Uh, lettuce and tomato.
钱是合法的吗  百分百合法
And this is legit, the money?  Hundred percent.
好  我加入  很好
Okay, I'm in.  Great.
能把我的手表还给我吗
Uh, can I get my watch back, please?
谢谢  还有她的
Thank you. And hers as well.
不  我...
No, I...
抱歉  没关系
Sorry.  It's okay.
我们有谁  我们有谁
Who do we have, who do we have?
艾薇呢  不  还在监狱里
What about Ivy?  No, still in jail.
真的吗  他呢
Really?  What about him?
那是男的  所以呢
Well, he's a him.  So?
不要男的
Don't want a him.
因为是他还是因为是"他"
Because it's a him or because it's a "Him"?
不  他不是什么重要人物
No, he's not a "Him."
我基本不认识他  那男的怎么了
I barely know the guy.  What's wrong with a him?
男的惹人注目  女的就不会
A him gets noticed, a her gets ignored,
这一次  我们不想引人注目
and for once, we wanna be ignored.
塔米呢
What about Tammy?
伙计
Hey, buddy,
能帮我个忙吗  你能出去玩吗
can you do me a favor? Can you take that outside?
黛比  我和我的家人在一起
Debbie, I am with my family.
我跟你说了...  我在外面
I told you...  I'm outside.
什么  我在你家车库
What?  I'm in your garage.
黛布
Deb?
黛布  你在这里干什么  我以为你在监狱
Deb, what are you doing here? I thought you were in jail.
我出来了
Mmm. I got out.
看看这些东西  我还以为你退休了呢
Look at all this. Thought you retired?
我是退休了
I did.
从加拿大偷运洗碗机
Not as exciting as hijacking trucks
总没有劫卡车来得刺激吧
that are smuggling dishwashers from Canada, right?
我已经不干了
Yeah, well, I don't do that anymore.
但是你很擅长
But you were so very good at it.
谢谢  嗯
Thank you.  Yeah.
这些都是你自己用的吗
So these are all for personal use, right?
你想要什么  就是想叙叙旧
What do you want?  Just wanna reconnect.
叙旧
Reconnect?
你一点都不无聊  对吧  塔塔
You're not bored out here, are you, TamTam?
对  我一点也不无聊
No, I'm not bored out here at all.
很好  很好  不无聊
Good, good.  No.
你为什么这么问  因为我需要一个销赃的
Why would you ask that?  Because I need a fence.
我告诉你我已经不干了  我退出了
Well, I told you I don't do that anymore. I'm out.
这是桩大活  我不在乎
It's a big job.  I don't care.
你要我告诉你这活有多大吗
Do you want me to tell you how big a job it is?
不  不  我不想听
No. No, I really don't.
我觉得我还是要告诉你这活有多大吧
I think I'm gonna tell you how big the job is.
你在开玩笑吗  没有
Are you kidding?  No.
妈妈  晚餐什么时候好啊  该死
Mommy, when's dinner ready?  Shit!
亲爱的  我马上来
Uh, sweetheart, I will be right there.
对不起  妈妈马上来
I'm so sorry. Mommy will be right there.
但是我好饿
But I'm hungry!
我知道  亲爱的  我保证我马上来
I know, sweetheart, I promise, I will be right there.
真是谢谢你了  她听上去很乖
Thanks a lot.  She sounds sweet.
这些都是怎么和你丈夫解释的
How do you explain all this to your husband?
网上淘的
eBay.
好了  大家伙儿  开始吧
Okay, everybody. Let's get started.
让我们给你们
We would like to present to you all
五月第一个周一
假设一种情况
with a hypothetical situation.
有多假设  不算太假设  除非我们搞砸了
How hypothetical?  Not very, unless we screw up.
每人的银行账户五周后
$16.5 million in each of your bank accounts,
多1650万美元
five weeks from now.
三周半后
In three and a half weeks,
大都会博物馆将会举办年度晚会
the Met will be hosting its annual ball,
庆祝他们的新展
celebrating its new costume exhibit,
而我们要去抢一笔
and we are going to rob it.
不是劫博物馆
Not the ball itself,
而是晚会上出现的
but a very important set of diamonds
一套非常珍贵的钻石
that will be attending the ball.
将会戴在达芙妮·克卢格的脖子上
On the neck of Daphne Kluger.
罗斯将会负责她的造型
Who Rose will be dressing.
杜桑  很好
The Toussaint?  Very good.
等达芙妮一不小心上了我们的贼船
Once Daphne is inadvertently onboard,
我们就可以把项链从卡地亚保险库拿出来
we can then get the necklace out of the Cartier vault,
黑掉大都会艺术博物馆安保系统  拜托你了  九球
hack the Met security system, thank you, Nine Ball,
潜入慈善晚会
and infiltrate the Gala,
最高级的晚会之一...
considered to be one of the most exclusive...
是最高级的
The most exclusive.
美国最高级的晚会邀请函
The most exclusive party invitation in America.
回家准备好你们的东西
So go home, get your affairs in order,
因为明天我们就要开始
because tomorrow, we begin pulling off
史上最大的珠宝抢劫行动
one of the biggest jewelry heists in history.
你要去哪里  我要去大城市
Where are you going?  I'm going to the big city.
多久  不太久  我保证
How long?  Uh, not too long, I promise.
我很快就会回来了
I'll be back before you know it.
你去做什么
What are you gonna do?
我要帮我朋友黛比的忙
I am going to help my friend Debbie with her job.
帮什么忙
What kind of job?
很复杂  我能跟你一起去吗
It's complicated.  Can I come with you?
不行  亲爱的  这是妈妈的特别出差
No, sweetie, this is Mommy's very special work trip.
是我的账户  我的钱
It is my account, it is my money,
我不能进入的唯一原因
and the only reason I can't access it
是因为我记不得我第二个表亲
is because I cannot remember the make and model
第一辆车的品牌和型号
of my second cousin's first car.
你能不能...
So if you could just...
我不想取钱
I don't wanna make a withdrawal,
我想存钱
I would like to make a deposit.
是的  我...
Yes, I...
我能...
Hey, can I...
没错  是的  我不会挂的  怎么了
Exactly, yes. Yes, I'll hold. What's up?
能不能给我一张地铁卡
Oh, hey, I was wondering if I can get a MetroCard,
因为我每天都从皇后区滑滑板过来
'cause I'm skateboarding in from Queens every day.
能给我一张地铁卡吗
Can I get a MetroCard?
我没有地铁卡
I don't have a MetroCard.
你没有地铁卡吗
You don't have a MetroCard?
我没有地铁卡
I don't have a MetroCard.
你是游客吗
What are you, a tourist?
你真有意思
You're fascinating.
你只给我二十美金
You're gonna just throw me one dub
买地铁卡吗  就这么多吗
for a MetroCard? That's it?
这样如何  我们偷五千万
How about this? We steal $50 million,
我给每个人都买一张地铁卡  怎么样
I'll buy everybody MetroCards. How's that?
好吧
Okay.
那是你哥哥吗  嗯
Is that your brother?  Mmmhmm.
他很帅  嗯
He's hot.  Mmm.
你确定他死了还是...
You sure he's dead or...
不确定
No.
是的  亲爱的  妈妈在做新工作了
Yes, sweetie, Mommy is in her new job now.
查理  你能帮我个忙吗
Charlie, will you do me a favor?
你能把那个放到那里吗
Can you put that right there?
什么  亲爱的
What, sweetheart?
是这样的...妈妈的工作是
Um, uh, well... Mommy...
发现非常特别的玩具
finds very special toys,
然后为它们找到新家
and then she finds new homes for them.
没错  就像你的乌龟  完全正确
Yes, exactly like your turtle. That is exactly right.
太感谢你了  查理  谢谢
Thank you so much, Charlie, thank you.
亲爱的  我得挂了
Sweetheart, I have to go.
我刚刚给黛比找了一个全新的玩具
I just got a brand new toy for Debbie,
我等不及要拿去玩了
and I can't wait to play with it.
锆石
Zirconium.
我喜欢  我知道你会喜欢的
I like it.  Yeah, I bet you do.
放开那个男人
Unhand the man.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
这是给你的特制眼镜
Here are your very special glasses.
假如罗斯能搞定  我是说假如
If Rose can pull this off, and that is a very big "If",
这副眼镜会扫描真项链
these glasses will scan the real necklace
然后把数字图像发给我们
and send a digital print back to us here.
一旦我们有了那个
Once we have that,
这个东西会用锆
this thing will print
打印出项链的复制品
a replica of the necklace in zirconium.
卡蒂亚
在哪里  这些不是杜桑
Where is it?  These are not the Toussaint.
我们以为你们可能想先看看这些
We thought you might want to see these first.
为什么
Right. What for?
那条项链的运输有些问题
There are certain logistical problems with that necklace.
我们都不知道如何投保
We wouldn't even know how to insure it.
好吧
All right.
"我们在电话上说得很清楚"
"We were very clear on the phone."
没错  我们在电话上说得很清楚
Yes. We were very clear on the phone.
我们只对杜桑感兴趣
We are only interested in the Toussaint.
没错
Yeah.
那样的话要谈很久了
Well, then, that would have to be a much longer discussion.
那条项链价值1.5亿美金
That necklace is valued at over $150 million.
我不太擅长跟数字打交道
Well, I'm not really a numbers person.
它需要专门的安保团队
It would require its own security team,
重新投保
a new insurance policy.
我敢确定你们肯定会解决这些细节问题的
I'm sure you'll work out all those details.
没那么简单
Oh, it's not that simple.
恐怕答案是不行
I'm afraid the answer is no.
不行吗
No?
不行
No.
听着  我能说句实话吗
Look, can I be frank?
我一直很喜欢卡地亚
I have always loved Cartier.
我觉得这里过去一直是史上
I think, historically, this has been
世界上最重要的公司
the most significant house in the world.
但是外面有一整代人
But there is whole generation out there
连公司的名字都念不准
who mispronounce your name.
法语很难
French can be difficult.
不  并不是
听着  我想要帮你...
如果你不想要我的帮助  我懂...
但是"杜桑"这样对你没好处
躺在保险库里...
它本可以...
让全世界为止痴迷...
挂在达芙妮·克卢格的大胸前
对
Oui.
无信号
别敲了
Stop it.
别敲了  没用的  住手  好吧  好吧
Stop it. That doesn't help. Stop.  Okay, all right. All right.
她们在地下太深了  接收不到信号
We're too far underground. Can't get a signal.
下面很安全啊
Very secure down here, huh?
五英尺厚实心混凝土
Five feet of solid concrete.
你说你想在光线下欣赏
You said you wanted to see it in the light.
你说你想在光线下欣赏项链
You wanted to see the necklace in the light.
没错
Right!
这有光线
This is light.
不不不  她说的是真正的光  自然光
No, no, no, she means real light. Natural light, yes.
走红毯是在太阳没下山的时候
The red carpet happens while the sun is still out.
不
Yes, no,
我认为这很重要  很重要
I'm afraid that's vital.  It's vital.
没错  我得在阳光下欣赏
Mmm. No, I must have the sun.
她一定要有阳光
She must have the sun.
这个光线怎么样  威尔女士  嗯...
How is this light, Ms. Weil?  Um...
很好  我们有阳光了
Yes, I think, yes, we have the sun.
好多了
Much better.
扫描中
有了  太好了
There it is!  All right.
你好  尤物
Hello, sexy.
快点  快点
Come on, come on.
威尔女士  她没事吧
Ms. Weil. Is she okay?
她没事  嗯
She's fine.  Hmm.
她得靠近看
She needs to take it in.
她就是这样
This is her process.
看起来非常棒
It looks really good.
太清楚了  没错
It's so clear.  Yeah.
快点
Come on.
不  好的  你得...
No, okay. You gotta...
不  好的
No. Yep.
如果你看好了  威尔女士...
If you are done, Ms. Weil...
...我们得...
...we'd like to...
...把项链送回保险库
...return this to the vault.
威尔女士
Ms. Weil?
Ms. Weil.
太棒了
Yes!
看好了
I'm done.
太棒了
Sweet.
天啊
Oh, my God!
好看吗  我说不好
Well?  I don't know.
你没感觉是因为这件只是用平纹细布做的样板
Well, you don't know because this is only a muslin.
首先  礼服会是粉色的
It's going to be pink, for a start.
我知道会是粉色的  但我感觉有哪里不对劲
I know it's going to be pink, but I don't know.
我觉得好像是腰部
Yeah, I feel like it's the waist.
我觉得腰部有点...还有臀部
I feel, like, it's just... And then the bottom.
我不太清楚臀部是不是合身
I don't know about the bottom.
我们可以改一下褶边
We can definitely change the hem.
是因为项链  不
It's the necklace.  Oh, no.
不是因为项链  就是因为项链
It's not the necklace.  It is the necklace.
很难看
It's just messy.
不不不  不难看
No, no, no, it's not messy.
难看是因为它是别针做的
It's messy 'cause it's safety pins.
不  你不要忘了钻石
No, you must remember the diamonds.
项链是钻石做的
It's gonna be diamonds.
我感觉我看起来很胖
I just feel like I look huge.
达芙妮  冷静  冷静  冷静
Hey, Daphne, come here. Come here. Come here.
听着  深呼吸...深呼吸
Listen, deep breath... Deep breath.
听着
Listen, look.
你的脖子是世界上最好看的
You've got one of the greatest necks in the world.
事实上  你的脖子是唯一
In fact, you've got the only neck
配得上这条项链的
that could carry this necklace off.
搭配你的脖子  这条项链...
With your neck, this necklace...
你将戴着它去参加大都会艺术博物馆慈善晚会
You are gonna walk into that Met Gala, and you
你将照亮天空
you are gonna light up the sky.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
如果你喜欢他  就向右滑
If you like him, you go right,
如果不喜欢...
and if you don't...
向左滑  没错  向左滑
I go left.  Yeah, you go left.
所以...  好的  听起来很容易
So...  Okay, that sounds easy.
那你喜欢他吗  我非常喜欢他
So do you like him?  Ooh. I like him a lot.
为什么
Okay, why?
他看上去很和善
He looks kind.
我要向右滑
I'm gonna swipe right.
配对成功  发送信息  继续滑动
好吧  天啊
Okay. All right.  Oh, my God!
这就是说...
So does that mean...
他也向右滑了  他也喜欢你
He liked you back! He likes you, too!
现在怎么办  现在怎么办
What happens now? What happens now?
你可以给他发信息  好的
So you can message him.  Okay.
你可以给他发送茄子的表情
And you can say, maybe, like, the eggplant emoji,
或者发做这个动作的女孩表情
or maybe the girl that does this.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
能帮我一下吗
Can you help me with something?
我有点迷路了
I think I'm a little lost.
当然  女士
Of course, ma'am.
我觉得我在绕圈
I feel like I'm going in circles.
我从埃及展区过来
I came from Egypt back there,
我要去海洋餐厅
and I'm trying to get to Oceana.
是会让人有点晕
It's a little confusing.
你可以从右边的楼梯下去
You can go down the stairs to your right,
或者可以回到进来的地方
or you can go back where you came from,
就在那下面  好的
right down there.  Okay.
可能有点远
It might take a little bit longer.
失陪一下  女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
借过一下  借过一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.
现在是早晨上班广播
Here's one for your morning commute.
昨晚  政治艺术家班克西
Last night, political artist Banksy
给了大都会博物馆一个大惊喜
made a surprise contribution to the Met.
我们的创世之母
Our founding mothers
昨晚出现在了大都会博物馆
appeared at the Met last night.
整点后15分为您播报交通情况
Traffic at 15 after the hour.
随时为您播报
Your news, all the time.
这是一次重大安保问题
This is a major security breach.
这怎么可能
How is this even possible?
他在泰特美术馆[英国]也干了
He did it at the Tate, too.
你是说
So you're saying
你们公司为我们博物馆设计的系统
the system your company designed for our museum
无法阻止像班克西这样的人...
does nothing to prevent someone like Banksy...
先生  我们更注重的是
Sir, we're a little more focused
东西不被盗走  而不是被偷偷放进来
on keeping things in than keeping things out.
麦卡利斯特安保公司
喂  是不是该道个歉
Hey! How about an "Excuse me"?
如果我错了  请纠正我
Correct me if I'm wrong.
你和你的公司负责
You and your company are responsible
监控和保护...
for monitoring and safeguarding...
要不要倒垃圾
Hey, want me to get the trash?
什么  不用
What? No.
你确定吗  你们这里有很多垃圾  伙计
You sure? 'Cause you got a lot here, buddy.
好吧  快点弄完
Fine. Just hurry it up.
博物馆
The museum's agreement
与你父亲公司的协议非常...
with your father's company is very...
充足  具体
Generous.  Specific.
祝你今晚愉快
Have a nice night.
董事会希望麦卡利斯特安保公司
The board expects McCallister Security
按照协议内容办事
to live up to the letter of that agreement.
我们将彻底检查一次系统
We'll do a full audit of the system
更新需要改动的任何地方
and update any part of it that needs to be changed.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
我们会进去修好  什么时候
We'll go in and fix it.  When?
立刻
Immediately.
既然我们知道他们
So, now that we've gotten them
要更改他们的系统
to make changes to their system,
我们也可以做一些改动  避免被发现
we can make changes, too, and not be detected.
你能把摄像头拉近一点吗
Can you pull up the cameras?
他们的镜头覆盖了每一个角落
They've got every inch of this place covered.
但是我们不在这里下手
But here is not where we're gonna hit it.
我们要在他们想都没想过的地方下手
We are gonna do it in a spot they don't even care about.
九球
Nine Ball.
纽约州的法律规定
Now it's a New York State law
任何公共洗手间内都不能安装摄像头
that no cameras can be mounted in a public bathroom.
那显然是侵犯个人隐私
Apparently, it's a privacy violation.
除非你喜欢侵犯
Unless you're into that.
我们一旦拿到"杜桑"
And once we get the Toussaint,
我们可以从那里把它弄走
we are gonna have to get it out of there
而不被发现
without being detected,
如果他们非常细致地
and they're gonna go over
检查他们的监控录像
their security footage with a finetooth comb,
从那个洗手间出来的任何人
and anyone seen exiting that bathroom
都会成为嫌疑犯
is gonna be a suspect.
所以...
So...
所以我们要有个带货的
So we get a mule.
别人可以帮我们带出来
Somebody else is gonna move it for us.
你在洗手间外面需要多少空间
How much space do you need outside
才能把东西藏到别人身上
that bathroom to plant it on somebody?
不知道  九英尺行吗
I don't know. Nine feet?
我们要多长时间
And how long is it gonna take us
可以建立九英尺的监控盲区
to build a ninefoot blind spot?
移动摄像头吗  嗯
Moving a camera?  Mmmhmm.
一点一点  需要10到12天
Bit by bit, 10, 12 days.
太好了
Great.
你策划这些花了多长时间
How long did it take you to figure all this out?
5年8个月12天
Five years, eight months, and 12 days.
大概这么久
Give or take.
卡地亚雇了
Cartier has hired
世界上最好的私人保镖
the best private security in the world.
圭勒莫·德维塔
Guillermo DeVita
做了教皇的安保主管十年
led the pope's security for 10 years.
众所周知  从来没有教皇被杀
And as you know, they've never lost a pope.
嗯  尤里·艾歇尔  前以色列情报机构
Mmm.  Yuri Eshel, former Mossad
摩萨德和国防军特种部队精英突击队成员
and IDF Special Forces, elite commando unit.
我非常肯定他们是杀手
I'm pretty sure they're assassins.
项链真的很漂亮  没错
Well, it's a nice necklace.  Yeah.
你可以把他们加入你的清单
So you can go ahead and just add them to your list.
什么清单  那个清单
What list?  That list.
这不是清单
It's not a list.
员工目录  大都会博物馆  麦卡利斯特员工
视觉矩阵设计  部门负责人  保罗
姓名  保罗·达曼尼恩
头衔  视觉矩阵设计  部门负责人
地点  麦卡利斯特安保公司纽约办公室
部门/客户  系统设计/大都会博物馆
他是谁
Okay. Who is he?
保罗·达曼尼恩  纽约州  纽约
简介: 儿子  兄弟  安保专家  爱尔兰软毛梗爱好者
麦卡利斯特安保视觉矩阵设计师
生活在纽约州纽约市
保罗的照片
爱尔兰软毛梗爱好者在哈里斯堡聚会
北美爱尔兰软毛梗协会
第八届年度爱尔兰软毛梗周末
5月17日到19日
宾州哈里斯堡  水库公园
跟同样喜欢爱尔兰软毛梗的人聚会
保罗
Oh, Paul.
痴迷爱尔兰软毛梗
忠诚  多情  低过敏性  梳毛提示
服务奖  保罗·达曼尼恩
保罗·达曼尼恩  麦卡利斯特安保
欢迎饲养员和梳毛员  点击此处  会员优惠和聚会
痴迷爱尔兰软毛梗
小可怜
You poor thing.
太可爱了
Look at that.
大都会博物馆摄像头分布图  2月4日
我们甚至不知道是不是班克西
We don't even know if it is Banksy.
可能是个模仿者
It could be an imitator.
保罗·达曼尼恩
麦卡利斯特安保
安全  稳固  可靠
摄像头分布  大都会博物馆摄像头分布
用户名  p_damanian
密码
就这点本事吗
That's all you got?
是否打开选中摄像头视频系统
很好
Sweet!
东北  大厅
下午好  Vogue[美国时尚杂志]
Good afternoon. Vogue.
谢谢你最后一刻过来
Thank you for coming in so last minute.
不客气  谢谢你给我面试机会
Oh, of course. Thank you for having me.
我猜你肯定听说了  我们的一名协调员去世了
I guess you heard, we lost one of our coordinators.
听起来很糟糕
Yes, and that sounded awful.
沙螨病
Chiggers.
我知道
I know.
那些到底是什么  好像是螨虫
What are those anyway?  It's like a mite, I think.
它钻进皮肤  在里面产卵
It burrows into the skin and lays its eggs inside.
然后它们孵化后再钻出来
And then they hatch and they dig their way out.
显然可以持续好几周
Apparently, it can last for weeks.
你肯定能胜任的
Well, you certainly seem qualified.
谢谢
Thank you.
也许还有点资历过高
Maybe overqualified.
怎么会有人资历过高呢
Well, how can anyone be overqualified?
毕竟这是大都会博物馆慈善"晚回"
This is the Met Gala after all.
晚会  大都会博物馆慈善晚会
Gala. Met Gala.
晚会  晚会
It's Gala.  Gala.
晚会对吗
Is it Gala?
没错  好的
Yeah.  Okay.
罗杰·费德勒再次
Roger Federer again
离下一个冠军只有一步之遥
one game away from another championship.
这里的球迷对费德勒的爱太疯狂了
The love for Federer in this place is just incredible.
安娜
Anna.
什么事
Uh, yeah?
你有个大都会博物馆员工岗位面试
You have that interview for the Met staff position.
你搞定吧  好的
Do it, do it.  Okay.
你不是认真的吧
You cannot be serious!
一记反拍直线获胜
A backhand downtheline win!
我们的办公桌真的不够用
We're really short on desk space,
所以你就在这里办公
so you'll be down here.
这边
This way.
这是你的办公桌  谢谢
Okay, so here is your desk.  Thank you.
克里斯提娜会帮你熟悉工作
And Christina will get you started.
好极了  非常感谢
Great. Thank you so much.
一天愉快  谢谢
Have a good day!  Thanks!
不好意思  什么事
Excuse me.  Yes?
刚才经过的是洗手间吗
Was that the bathroom that we passed?
对  就在走廊尽头
Oh, yes, just down the hall.
谢谢
Thank you.
难以置信
This is unbelievable.
大都会博物馆慈善晚会座位图
那是李奥吗
That's Leo?
小李子吗
LeoLeo?
只有一个李奥
There's only one Leo.
天啊  泰勒·斯威夫特
Oh, my God! Taylor Swift!
你这口气也太像白人妹了
You're so white!
我们不能只去参加晚会吗  非得偷东西吗
Can't we just go to this? Do we have to steal stuff?
是的
Yes!
她坐在哪里  四号桌  十点钟方向
Where is she?  Table four, 10:00.
正对着洗手间
Straightest shot to the bathroom
位置很好
without putting her in Siberia.
达芙妮·克卢格
她旁边有个空位
There's a blank spot next to her.
是给她的男伴的
It's for her date.
男伴是谁
Who's her date?
我不知道
I don't know.
你好  你好  抱歉打扰一下
Hi.  Hi. I'm sorry to interrupt,
我这边整理好了主席晚宴的
but I've got the final guest list
最终宾客名单
for the Chairman's Dinner.
很好
Oh, great.
你确认他们的到达时间了吗
You have all their arrival times?
所有人的到达时间
All their arrival times,
包括底下的一些附加人员
including a few additional names at the bottom.
克劳德·贝克
Claude Becker?
他的公关人员很感兴趣
His publicist was into it.
我都不用开口
I barely had to ask.
晚会前主席晚宴
你好
Hello.
他们让我坐你旁边
They put me next to you.
那我很幸运
Oh, lucky me.
你好
Hello.
克劳德·贝克
Claude Becker.
达芙妮·克卢格
Daphne Kluger.
自大狂已就位
The ego has landed.
你以前怎么会爱上这种蠢货
How did you ever fall for this schmuck?
说真的
Seriously?
我和卢以前过得很苦
Lou and I were going through a rough patch,
而我真的想自己闯一番天地
and I really wanted a big score of my own.
他拉拢了你
So he roped you in?
也不是
Mmm. Not really.
怎么  他跟你说了实话
What, told you the truth?
只有这样才能骗到一个骗子  不是吗
Only way to con a con, right?
我和卢当时在装配宾果游戏
Lou and I were rigging Bingo
十年前
新泽西州  帕塞伊克
西部宾果游戏厅
还在轮盘赌局里骗点小钱
and running cheap cons at Roulette.
运气好的话一晚上能赚一千
Lucky if we made $1,000 a night.
宾果  有人胜出
Bingo!  Bingo call.
我的一个朋友给我介绍了这位艺术商
So a friend of mine set me up with this art dealer
我们琢磨出了一个简单的骗局
and we worked out a simple little hustle.
我找克劳德·贝克  那边
Claude Becker?  Right through there.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好  我是黛比
Hi. I'm Debbie.
克劳德·贝克
Claude Becker.
当有人对某件作品感兴趣的时候
When somebody got interested in a piece,
我就扮作另一个买家抬高价格
I'd pose as another buyer and drive up the price.
赚到的数目很不错  他的厨艺也很好
Money was good and he was great in the kitchen.
天哪  真美味
Oh, my God, it's so good.
有一天
One day
他让我扮作卖家  而不是买家
he asked me to pose as the seller, not the buyer.
你怎么做
What did you do?
这个嘛
Well...
一个签名  价值50万
One signature, half a million dollars.
他说那很简单
He said it was simple.
我把证明文件给他们  他们就给我一张支票
I'd hand them the documents, and they'd slide me a check.
最多几分钟就能搞定
The whole thing would take a couple minutes, tops.
抱歉我们来晚了
Sorry we're late.
不晚  没关系
Not at all.  It's okay.
幸会  幸会
Very nice to meet you.  It's a pleasure.
作品很美  我们很喜欢
It's a beautiful piece.  Oh, we just love it!
他说对了  的确很快
He was right. It all happened very quickly.
你有权请律师
You have a right to an attorney.
如果你请不起律师...
If you cannot afford an attorney...
那不是我的画  画是她拿来的
It wasn't my painting. She brought the picture to me.
证明文件和签名都是她搞的
She had documentation, signatures.
你们是恋爱关系吗
And you two were dating?
什么
What?
我什么也不会说的
Not saying a word.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
因为他的嘴可不像你这么紧
'Cause he's not being quite as tightlipped as you are.
这些是你的签字吗
Are these your signatures?
好  我会作证的
Yeah, I will testify.
我也被骗了  好吗
I was defrauded too, right?
我就在外面
I'll be right outside.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
你最好告诉我事情不是我想的那样
You better tell me this is not what I think this is.
什么
What?
克劳德·贝克
Claude Becker.
不是我干的
I didn't do that.
我不是庄荷  好吗
I'm not a croupier, okay?
也不是口袋里响叮当的游客
Or a tourist with a bucket of quarters.
别想骗我
Don't con me.
你不能设局中局
You do not run a job in a job!
没关系的
It's not going to matter.
我们会被抓的
We are going to get caught.
别说了  不会的
Stop it. We're not.
你为什么要这么做
Why do you do this?
就不能好好干桩活吗
Why can't you just do a job?
为什么非得加点别的
Why does there always have to be an asterisk?
你设计他  我不干了
You frame him, I walk.
别这样
Stop.
和上一回一模一样
This is just like last time.
卢  卢
Lou. Lou!
卢
Lou.
他害我进了监狱
He sent me to jail!
你无法想象我的感受
You have no idea what that's like.
好吧  他会故技重施的
Yeah, well, he's gonna do it again.
不  他不会的
No, he's not.
不会的
He's not.
很好  切换摄像头
Good. Switching cameras.
我现在走向洗手间
Walking towards the bathroom.
好  进去盲区
Okay, in the blind spot.
我继续往前走
I'm gonna keep walking.
没有
Nothin'.
好了  你出现在监控里了
Okay, you're right there.
30.5厘米  干得漂亮
12 feet. Nice job!
谢了  九球
Thank you, Nine Ball.
很简单  小事一桩
That easy. Don't mention it.
对你来说有难的吗
What's hard?
抱歉  我知道这个
Sorry, listen, I know this really
跟我没什么关系...
isn't any of my business...
不  你说
No, go ahead.
只是有点小问题
It's just a little red flag here.
这个酒席承办公司没有配营养专家
But this caterer doesn't have a nutritional specialist.
好的  我们手头
Okay.  And we're running
有20%的餐点必须特别配餐
at 20% special meals.
素食  无麸质  低钠  去乳糖
Vegan, glutenfree, low sodium, lactose.
我以前有个客户因此被告了
I had a client get sued.
真的吗  对
Really?  Yeah.
我觉得我们得做好一切准备
I don't think we should wing any of this stuff.
我觉得我们缺个人
I think we are short a staff person.
得找个营养学家
We need a nutritionist.
我倒是认识一个人  是吗
I do know someone.  You do?
对  她很厉害
Yeah, and she's great.
她刚从澳大利亚搬来
She just moved here from Australia.
对
Yes.
好的  去吧
Okay. Go.
自动售货机  走廊  走廊
Vendor, hallway, hallway.
路过礼堂
Past the auditorium.
走廊  走廊  走廊  入口
Hallway, hallway, hallway, entry.
我来了  抱歉来晚了  路上太堵了
Hi, hi! I'm so sorry I'm late. Traffic was horrible.
好吧
Okay...
阿米塔  谢谢
Amita.  Thank you.
康斯坦丝
Constance.
九球
Nine Ball.
卢
And Lou.
还有罗斯
And Rose.
谢谢
Thank you.
还有黛比你的  谢谢
And Debbie.  Thank you.
大家好  我是达芙妮·克卢格
Hi, I'm Daphne Kluger,
接下来是今年晚会的定制时装  让我们先睹为快
and this is your sneak peek of this year's Costume Institute.
这是D&G的  那是加利亚诺为迪奥的设计
This is Dolce and that's Galliano for Dior.
那个是麦昆的
And that is McQueen.
明天谁为你造型呢
And who's dressing you tomorrow?
罗斯·威尔
Mmm. Rose Weil.
有意思的选择  我知道
Interesting.  I know.
算是个意外的选择
I kind of thought it was an unexpected choice.
这些是什么
What's this over here?
来自八个欧洲皇室家族的珍宝
So these are the crown jewels from eight royal families of Europe.
所以这里才会有个水池
Which is probably why there's a moat.
我们不能过去看吗  天哪  当然不行
So we can't go over there?  No. God, no.
我希望我们可以  话说回来
I wish we could. Anyway...
这些都是我们问德里特里·某某借来的
Uh, they are on loan to us from Dmitri
那个俄罗斯名字太长我不会念
VeryLongRussianLastName that I can't pronounce.
我们听说晚会中展示的珠宝
We hear those aren't the only jewels
不仅仅只有这些
that'll be on display.
谁告诉你的  我有渠道
Who told you?  I have sources.
好吧  既然风声已经走漏了...
Well, since the cat's already out of the bag...
是的  我将会佩戴一条
Yes, I will be wearing a necklace
卡蒂亚出借的项链
that Cartier has decided to loan me.
名叫"杜桑"
It's called the Toussaint,
它已经被锁在保险箱里50年了
and it has been in a vault for 50 years.
我有点兴奋
And I'm just a little excited.
你试戴过了吗  也许
Have you tried it on already?  Maybe.
有多少克拉  够多了
How many carats is it?  Enough.
五月的第一个周一
口红颜色  你觉得怎么样
Lipstick. What do you think?
粉色  娃娃粉
Pink. Um, yeah. Barbie.
很好看
In a good way.
谢谢
Thank you.
项链到了  好  终于啊
It's here.  Right. Finally. Great.
好了
All right.
你还没看过  没有
Oh, you haven't seen it.  No.
你好  你好
Hello.  Hello.
真是个大箱子
Ooh. That's a big box.
好了
All right.
天哪
Holy crap!
那我们
Should we, uh...
我们试戴一下  看看合不合适
Let's try it on. See if it fits.
好
Okay.
我可以...  请吧
Can I, uh...  Sure.
很沉
Wow. That's heavy.
真的很沉
Really heavy.
到我这儿来
Come to mama.
可能会有点...
All right. It might be a little...
有点凉
Just a tad cold. Right.
好了
All right. Okay.
我看看  好
Let me see. Right.
戴好了
That goes in.
看啊
Look at you.
好了  搞定
Yep. There.
很合适
It fits.
好
All right.
很合适
It fits.
好了
Right, okay.
先把项链取下来  我们再试试礼服
We can get it off, and then we can try the frock.
好  等一下
Okay.  Um... Hang on.
抱歉  你取不下来的  得让我来
Sorry, you cannot do it. I have to do it.
需要特制磁铁才能取下
It requires a special magnet.
什么  厉害
What?  Cool.
特制磁铁  对
Uh, special magnet?  Yes.
这招不错
That's cool.
这招很妙  非常妙
That's brilliant. Brilliant.
厉害
Amazing.
我能不能
Can I, uh...
我能不能再看一次  我有点好奇
Can I just see that again, out of interest?
可以  谢谢
Sure.  Thanks.
真厉害
That's amazing.
真不错  让我看看是怎么弄的
Great. Let me just see. So how does it work?
海达·施耐德  《明镜周刊》的时尚记者
Hilda Schneider, fashion reporter, Der Spiegel.
不行
No.
海达·施耐德  外交官
Hilda Schneider, diplomatic attache?
不行
No.
汉莎资产公司  汉莎
Lufthansa asset?  Lufthansa.
出问题了
Problem.
什么问题  罗斯发来的
With?  From Rose.
老天
Oh, God.
别啊
Come on!
我的天  真厉害
Oh, my God, that is amazing.
只有用磁铁才能取下来
And you can only do it with a magnet?
只有用磁铁才可以  让我看看...
Only the magnet.  Let me just see...
停  回放一遍
Stop. Play it again.
我的天  真厉害
Oh, my God, that is amazing.
只有用磁铁才能取下来
And you can only do it with a magnet?
只有用磁铁才可以  放大一点
Only the magnet.  Zoom in a little bit.
怎么了  莱斯利  我很忙的
What, Leslie? I'm busy.
莱斯利
Leslie?
姐们  我们遇到点问题
Hey, sis, we're in a bit of a jam right now,
需要你帮把手
and I need your help.
看起来他们用的是聚合磁铁和弹簧
So it seems like they used polymagnets and a spring.
磁铁会在同一轴上
It gives you attraction and repulsion
产生吸引和排斥  懂吗
in the same axis, you know?
不太懂  磁铁聚合在一起
Not really.  Well, they're drawn together.
但没有接触  直到你转动磁铁
But don't touch, until you rotate it,
它们就会锁死
and then they lock.
很厉害  我去找一对
It's real dope. I'll go get you a positive
正极和负极回路  应该可以用
and a negative pole in a loop. That oughta work fine.
你真是个小天才  姐们  谢了
You're a little genius, sis. Thank you.
真的吗  她解决了
Really? She fixed it?
真的吗  你还用问吗
Really? You just asked me that?
好了  确认声音
Okay, you guys. Sound check.
九球  确认
Nine Ball.  Check.
黛比  确认
Debbie.  Check.
康斯坦丝  确认
Constance.  Yeah.
阿米塔  确认
Amita.  Yep.
卢  确认
Lou.  Check.
那烂活儿忙死我了  还被警察追了
That shit was hectic. Got chased by a cop!
好吧  这是我妹妹维罗妮卡  各位
Okay, so this is my sister, everyone, Veronica.
你看看  疯了
Check this out. Crazy.
干得漂亮  我欠你一次  小家伙
Tight. All right. I owe you one, you little shit.
给我弄个新证件
Just get me a new ID.
回家去吧
Go home.
你爸妈做什么的
What do your parents do?
好了  我们开始  大家都在吗
Okay, we are up. Is everybody on?
在
Yes.
好了  女士们  半小时
All right, ladies. Half an hour.
倒计时开始
Countdown starting now.
好了  首先  不需要紧张
Okay. First. No need to be nervous.
监狱里的饭菜比大多数人
The food is better on the inside
想象中好得多
than most people think
就连关禁闭都算得上平静
and even solitary can be kind of peaceful.
我只想说  谢谢你
I just wanna say, thank you.
过去三周对我来说很奇妙
The last three weeks have been amazing for me,
为了这个时刻我们努力了很久
and we've all worked very hard for this moment.
所以无论今晚发生了什么
So whatever happens tonight,
我想要你记住一件事
I want you to remember one thing,
你不是为我而做这件事
you are not doing this for me.
也不是为你自己
You are not doing this for you.
某个地方有一个八岁的小女孩
Somewhere out there is an eightyearold girl
正躺在床上  梦想着成为一个罪犯
lying in bed, dreaming of being a criminal.
这是为她而做的
Let's do this for her.
请不要与宾客随意交谈
Do not engage in informal conversation with the guests, please.
不要随身携带手机
Do not have your cell phone on you.
活动开始前  请确保手机
Please make sure your cell phone is turned in
已经交至安全主管
to security prior to the start of the event.
非常重要的一点
Very important.
不要无精打采  不要双手抱胸
Do not slouch, cross your arms,
或者把手插到口袋里
put your hands in your pockets.
我明白今晚很长
I know it's gonna be a long night.
我知道你们会感到累
I know you're gonna get tired.
你好  你好吗
Hello.  Hello. How are you?
爱德华  很高兴看到你  这位是克劳德·贝克
Edward, so good to see you. Claude Becker.
幸会  还有这位  罗斯·威尔
Pleasure.  And, of course, Rose Weil.
你们认识吗  认识
You two know each other?  Yes.
天哪  这是杜桑吗
My dear, is that the Toussaint?
你看起来身价百万
I'd say you look like a million bucks,
但这项链可是价值一亿啊
but it's more like 100 million.
谢谢  不过是价值1.5亿
Thank you, it's a 150 million actually.
今晚造型的灵感来源是什么
What inspired you for tonight's look?
她
Her.
难以置信  今晚的亮点在哪里
Unreal. So what makes this such a fun night?
你永远不知道你会见到谁
I mean, you never know who you're gonna see.
整个世界的明星都聚集在这里
It's stars from all over the planet.
你会见到演员  来自时尚产业的人
Meeting actors, people in the fashion industry.
接下来这一位  塞雷娜·威廉姆斯[网球名将]
So coming up next, we have Serena Williams.
你好吗  我很好  你呢
How are you?  I'm good. How are you?
我很好  谢谢你
I'm good, thank you.
你征服了网球场  你还是一位好母亲...
So you've conquered the court, you've conquered motherhood...
我在努力  你功成名就
I'm trying.  I mean, you are succeeding.
抱歉  我们得确认下名单  请问您的姓名
Sorry, we're a little backed up today. Your name?
海达·施耐德
Uh, Hilda Schneider.
找到了  祝您今晚愉快
Oh, here it is. Have a good night.
抱歉  抱歉  哇  我喜欢你的裙子
谢谢
是老款了  别告诉别人  保证不说
看这边  海蒂[名模]  海蒂
Here, Heidi! Heidi!
好的  准备好了吗
Yes. Ready for tonight?
你好  很高兴见到你  太好了
Hi, how are you?  Nice to see you! Fantastic.
准备坐下
Ready to sit.
辣酱吗  辣酱
Hot sauce?  Hot sauce.
你自己没问题吧  没问题  回见
You good?  Yeah. I'll see you soon?
不做了  我们打烊了
Hey, no, we're closed.
已经打烊了
We're closed.
别啊  我都看见了
Come on, dude. It's right there.
找到她了
Yeah, I got her.
我看见她了
Yeah, I see her.
可以行动
We're a go.
大家好
Hi, everybody.
你好  你好吗
Hi.  How are you?
你好  很高兴见到你
Hi. Good to see you.
很高兴见到你  你看上去美极了
It's so good to see you. You look amazing.
你也是  干杯  干杯
You too. Cheers.  Oh, yeah, cheers.
不不  是真的
No, no, these are real.
非常感谢  你人真好
Thank you very much. So kind of you.
好了  倒计时
Okay, counting down.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
第八桌要
Need a glutenfree
无麸质餐点和烤鱼
and a broiled fish for Table Eight.
第四桌的素食在哪里
Where's the vegan for Table Four?
在这
Over here.
快送上去
Go, go, go.
天啊终于来了
Oh, God!
我饿死了
I'm so hungry.
我三天都没吃东西了
Mmm. I haven't eaten anything in three days.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我太失礼了吗
Am I being rude?
她吃了很多
She's in deep.
差不多半碗
Maybe half a bowl.
这时候你必须行屈膝礼
So, you're supposed to curtsy.
他们那儿还有个人会教你怎么行屈膝礼
They actually have a guy there to teach you how to curtsy.
对  真的有
Yes, that's true.
总之  我进去了  我弯了弯膝盖
Anyway, I go in, I'm doing this little knee bend.
然后女王怒视着我
And the Queen glares at me
对我说"这可不是屈膝礼"
and says, "That's not a curtsy."
真的吗
Really?
结果  我因为屈膝礼
So now, I am in a curtsy standoff
跟英国女王僵持不下
with the Queen of England.
还有...
And...
你没事吧
Are you okay?
嗯  我没事  没事  只是...
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine. I just...
你要去洗手间吗
Do you need to go to the bathroom?
不用  我没事  你确定吗
No! I'm fine.  Are you sure?
我因为屈膝礼跟女王...
I'm at this curtsy standoff with Queen...
而她...  你没事吧
And she's...  Are you okay?
没事  等一下
I'm fine. Just give me one second,
等等  我得...
hold on. I just need to get this...
你还好吧
You all right?
好戏开始
Game on!
请让一下  我们必须...
Excuse me, we need to...
很好
That's good.
你正在盲区边缘
Okay, you're right on the edge of the blind spot.
你还好吗
Hey, you all right?
还好吗  小可怜
You good? Oh, you poor thing.
没事的  你会没事的  呼吸  呼吸
It's okay. You'll be okay. Breathe, breathe...
呼吸  呼吸
Breathe... Breathe...
呼吸
Breathe.
好了  十秒
Okay, ten seconds.
开始
Here we go.
你  过来
Hey, come here.
这些盘子不能留在这儿
This can't be here. You need to
你得马上送去厨房
get this into the kitchen right away.
好的  好了  快去
No problem.  Okay, go. Go, go.
看你的了  黛比
Coming at you, Deb.
好  看见他了
Okay, here he comes.
好了  带货的出来了
Okay, my mule is out.
各位女士未暴露
All my ladies still in the dark.
兄弟  兄弟
Dude. Dude.
你有那个吗  什么
You have it?  Have what?
我抽了
Oh, I smoked it.
你抽了  什么意思
What do you mean, "Smoked it"?
乔什问我
You know, Josh asked,
"你有没有..."
and he was like, "Hey, do you have..."
他人呢  出什么事了
Guys, where is he? What's wrong?
怎么回事
What's happening?
他在走廊停下了  在跟人聊天
Stalled in the hallway. Chitchattin'.
塔米  你得让他快走
Tammy, you got to get him moving now.
我把汤放下  然后...
I'm putting the soup down, I'm like...
喂  你们在干什么
Hey! Hey, what the hell are you guys doing?
我们付工资不是让你们来聊天的
You're not getting paid to talk.
快点  好  抱歉
Let's go, come on.  Yeah, sorry.
放这边  给我  我来洗
Here, I'll take those. I'll take those.
谢了
Thanks.
我去上个厕所  我去上个厕所
Bathroom break. Bathroom break!
真是千钧一发
That was intense.
怎么了
What?
我不知道  可能掉在了那边
I don't know. It could've fallen off in there.
也可能掉在了之前那边  我不确定
It could've fallen off back there. I'm not sure.
我吐得肠子都快出来了
I was just barfing my guts out.
我一直在餐桌旁坐着
I was back at the table the whole time.
封锁出口
Seal the exits.
什么  不  有必要
What? No. Do we have to make
把事情闹这么大吗  拜托
such a big deal about this? Come on.
锁住出口  拜托
You better lock it up.  Oh, come on!
我们必须清场  不可以
We need to clear the room.  You can't do that.
我们必须地毯式搜查
We need to do a full sweep.
不可能
We can't.
你知道现场都来了谁吗
Do you know who's here?
价值1.5亿的项链在此丢失了
You just lost $150 million.
如果伦勃朗的画作丢失了  你会怎么做
What would you do if it was a Rembrandt missing, hmm?
晚宴很快会重新开始  我保证
Dinner will resume shortly, I promise!
感谢你们的理解
Thank you so much for your understanding.
请从楼梯下楼
Just walk towards the stairs.
正在封锁出口
Sealin' the exits.
各位  两人一组
Gentlemen, we're working in teams of two.
从四周向内部搜索
We start at the perimeter and work our way in.
扫描完成后
Once you've been scanned,
请直接前往出口
please go directly to the exit.
那里会有人
There will be someone there
告诉你往哪里走
that will show you where to go.
你知道发生什么事了吗
Do you know what's going on here?
丢失了一件物品
An item seems to have been lost.
他们正在寻找
They're looking for it now.
你知道丢了什么吗  钻石
Do you know what they lost?  Diamonds.
很多钻石
Lots of diamonds.
钻石  真的吗  让我们等在这儿是为了找钻石
Diamonds? Really? We're waiting around for diamonds?
我真的得去洗手间
Sir, I really just need to go to the bathroom.
好了  有情况了
Okay, shit's blowing up.
警察来了  卡蒂亚的人来了
Police coming, Cartier coming.
一大堆新闻记者也来了
A bunch of news people coming.
对
Yeah.
对  她们正在操作
Yeah, they're doing it.
做到一半了
They're about halfway through.
你离开餐桌去洗手间的路上  做了什么事
Was there anything you did or anyone you talked to
有没有跟什么人交谈过
between your table and the bathroom?
要是你没注意到的话
I was rather preoccupied at the time,
我当时急得不行
in case you didn't notice.
阿米塔  厨房来了个人
Amita, there's a guy in the kitchen.
再给我几分钟
Just give it a few more minutes.
没有几分钟了
We don't have a few minutes.
该死的
Oh, shit!
他到你那儿了
He's right there.
塔米  你快到了吗  你在哪里
Tammy, how close? Where are you now?
在水池边
By the moat.
塔米  把项链从水里捞起来
Tammy, pull it out of the water.
把项链放水里  然后捞起来  快
Just plant it in the water! Just pull it out, right now!
找到了
Found it!
在水里  肯定是你跑的时候
It was in the water. It must have fallen off
掉到水里了
while you were running.
我看看
May I?
找到了
We got it back.
好  我马上下来
Okay. I'll come back down.
康斯坦丝  你做得很好
Constance, you good.
厉害
Whoa, sick!
胶水还没干  胶水还没干
Uhuh. There's glue, there's glue!
感觉好点了吗
Feeling better?
好点了
I do now.
来两杯苏格兰威士忌
Couple scotches, please.
不好意思
祝你好运
我的上帝
Dear God!
谢谢
Thank you.
这里很好
Very nice.
首先
First of all,
我不是执法机构的人
I'm not a member of law enforcement.
我是与保险公司合作的
I work with the insurance carrier.
也就是说  我是前来调查是否存在骗保
Which means I'm either looking for fraud
又或者鉴定项链是否是真品
or I'm looking for the real necklace.
除此之外我都不关心
Beyond that, I couldn't care less.
恐怕两者的答案都是否定的
I'm afraid you won't find either here.
我们拭目以待  先生
We'll see about that, Monsieur...
这位...  德拉鲁·布鲁萨尔
Monsieur?  DelarueBroussard.
好的
Okay.
劳伦斯  你觉得
Lawrence, when did you last see
你最后一次见到真品是什么时候
what you believe to be the authentic item?
送去大都会博物馆晚会现场的时候
When it left here for the Met Gala.
你什么时候知道这是赝品的
When did you know this was a fake?
它被送回来的那一刻
The moment it was returned.
还有你们两位
And you two.
你们一整晚
You had your eyes on the necklace
都看着项链吗
the entire evening?
除了克卢格小姐在公共卫生间里
Apart from when Miss Kluger had her
不幸的身体不适事件发生时
unfortunate incident in the public toilet.
没错
That's correct.
你们陪同她入内了吗
Did you accompany her inside?
那是女卫生间
It's a women's bathroom.
那是条非常贵重的项链
It's a very big necklace.
洗手间只有一个出入口
There is only one entrance in and out.
我们就在门口守着
We were stationed at the door.
你们检查下水管道了吗
Did you check the plumbing?
没有  我检查了
No.  I did.
好  继续往里
Okay, keep going forward.
可以说非常干净
Squeaky clean, so to speak.
偷走项链的人
Whoever stole this necklace
设法逃过检测出门了
managed to get out without being detected.
也就是说我们要找的人非常聪明
Which means we're looking for someone very smart.
先生们
Gentlemen.
我见过一匹纯种赛马
I've seen a thoroughbred racehorse
被扔进树木粉碎机
thrown into a tree shredder.
人们为了骗保
People will go to great lengths
什么都干得出来
to defraud an insurance carrier.
这个  这是什么
There! What's this?
我说了这不是盲区
I'm saying that's not a blind spot.
那是什么  洗手间
What do you call that then?  The bathroom.
我看不到洗手间啊
I don't see a bathroom.
那是...
That's...
那是因为在盲区里
Because it's in the blind spot.
在洗手间能偷到什么东西
What can someone steal from a bathroom anyway?
我不知道  化妆品
I don't know, toiletries,
薄荷糖  手巾
mints, hand towels,
显然还有一条6磅重的钻石项链
a sixpound diamond necklace, apparently.
这是谁
Now, who's this?
一个侍者吧
A busboy?
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
我怎么会认识侍者
How would I know a busboy?
你是上流社会的人吗
Aren't we posh?
进出博物馆的每个人我不是都认识
I don't know everyone who goes in and out of the museum.
你在意一个侍者干什么
Why do you care about a busboy?
出问题的时间段里  他是唯一一个
He's the only person who moves in and out of the blind spot
进出盲区的人
during the period in question.
你能别把那里叫做盲区了吗
Could you please stop calling it a blind spot?
好吧
Fine.
由于你独特的摄像头放置
The bathroom door that we can't see
那扇我们看不到的洗手间的门
because of your unique camera placement.
这是世界上最先进的博物馆安保系统
This is the most sophisticated museum security in the world.
每一件艺术品旁都设有多个角度的摄像头
Every piece of art is recorded from multiple angles.
我们只是不需要在洗手间保护艺术品
We just don't happen to keep art in the bathroom.
我不是批评家  凯尔
I'm not a critic, Kyle.
我是保险调查员
I'm an insurance investigator.
我不想那么做的
I didn't wanna do it.
但是埃里克一直在撺掇我
But Eric's all, like, "Come on!"
我表示我不想再这么做了
I'm, like, "Dude, I don't do that anymore."
他说人人都这么做
He's, like, "Everyone's out on the loading dock!"
我知道我很愚蠢
I know it was really stupid.
我知道我是个混蛋
I know I'm an asshole,
可那大麻都不是我的
but it wasn't even my weed.
抱歉  你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
那大麻不是我的  你想要我
It wasn't my weed! Do you want me
尿在杯子里或是怎么样吗
to pee in a cup or something?
不  不必了
No, that won't be necessary.
你确定吗  我没关系的
Are you sure? I really don't mind.
我很肯定
I'm positive.
他们给我戴上了项链
They put the necklace on me.
然后我走了红毯
Then I walked the red carpet.
然后我看了展
Then I saw the exhibit.
然后我喝了汤
Then I ate my soup.
然后我吐得肠子都要出来了
Then I hurled my guts out.
然后项链就丢了
Then the necklace was gone.
然后大家就都抓狂了
And then everybody freaked out.
然后他们又找回了项链  我以为
And then they found it again, I thought.
结果不是吗
But, no?
这位先生
This gentleman.
克劳德·贝克
Claude Becker.
他是我的男伴
He was my date.
你戴着项链期间
Was there ever a time you two were alone
有没有跟他独处过
while you were wearing the necklace?
没有
No.
你在洗手间的时候有人跟你在一起吗
Anyone present with you in the bathroom?
我头埋在马桶里呢
My head was in a toilet bowl.
那之后呢
How 'bout after?
很多人
A lot of people.
你认识这个女人吗
Do you know this woman?
不认识
No.
黛比·奥申  重罪犯
Debbie Ocean, convicted felon.
她的哥哥  丹尼·奥申
Her brother, Danny Ocean,
犯过更多重罪
more convicted felon.
事情发生当晚她在场
She was present on the night of the incident.
是她偷了项链吗
Did she steal the necklace?
显然不是  她是唯一一个有不在场证明的
Apparently not, she's the only one with an alibi.
全程对着摄像头微笑
Smiling at the camera the entire time.
所以...
Ooh. So...
所以我现在手头有五个履历清白的人有嫌疑
So I have five innocent people who seem to be suspects,
而某个最有可能是嫌犯的人  却不是嫌犯
and someone who should be a suspect but isn't.
我手头的摄像头
I have cameras
覆盖了博物馆的每个角落
covering every inch of the museum,
除了洗手间
except for the loo,
而价值1.5亿的项链就在那里  在你的脖子上被偷了
where $150 million was stolen from that neck, your neck.
有意思的案件
Interesting case.
有时候我真爱我的工作
Some days, I love my job.
我也爱我的工作
I love my job, too.
你们完蛋了
You guys are fucked.
地方不错
Nice place.
这么大要开暖气可够费劲的
It must be a bitch to heat.
打扰一下  你这是私闯民宅
Excuse me! You are trespassing.
不  是我们邀请她来的
No. We asked her to come.
你们邀请她来的
You asked her to come?
几天前我们发现克卢格小姐...
We realized a few days ago that Miss Kluger...
不是个货真价实的蠢货
Was not a total fricking idiot.
她好像感觉到了我们要做什么
Might have gotten a sense of what we were doing.
你的脖子是世界上最好看的
You've got one of the greatest necks in the world.
首先  有一件事我很看得出来
First of all, if there's one thing I know,
糟糕的演技
it's bad acting.
事实上  你的脖子是唯一
In fact, you've got the only neck
配得上这条项链的
that could carry this necklace off.
而且我几乎从来不会吐
And I almost never throw up.
就算我喝得很醉
Even when I'm really wasted.
在水里
It was in the water.
肯定是你跑的时候掉到水里了
It must have fallen off while you were running.
最后  重要的是
And last but not least,
我见过的人永远不会忘
I never forget a face.
黛比·奥申
Debbie Ocean.
好吧  所以
Yeah. Yeah. So,
我觉得  8个人分1.5亿
seems to me, eight shares of 150 million
总比7个人什么都分不到要好  对吧
is better than seven shares of nothing, right?
怎么对我这么冷淡
Chilly!
你好  达芙妮  欢迎加入我们
Hi, Daph! Welcome to the team!
没必要击掌庆贺
Let's not all highfive at once.
再说了  我可是把你们从保险诈骗罪中
Plus, I am the one who is saving your asses
拯救出来了  什么
from insurance fraud.  What?
保险诈骗罪  我刚要说到这个
Insurance fraud?  I was gonna get to that.
什么时候的事
When?
他们似乎派出了一名保险调查员
It seems that they've assigned an insurance investigator...
他会把你们里里外外查个遍
Who's about to look up your ass with a flashlight.
谁  神探科伦坡转世
Who?  This little Columbo dude,
一模一样  除了不穿风衣
everything but the trench coat.
绝对会查到你头上
Totally on to you.
他叫约翰·弗雷泽
His name is John Frazier.
你认识他  对
You know him?  Yes.
他抓了我爸爸两次  我哥哥一次
He busted my father twice and my brother once.
老熟人了
He's family.
好了  以防大家忘记
All right. Lest we forget,
这个计划说好了我不会坐牢的
this entire enterprise was to keep me out of jail.
没人会坐牢的
Hey. No one's going to jail.
你确定吗  我们料到了这种情况
Are you sure?  We expected this.
早就做了准备
We prepared for this.
对  很显然
Yup, that's clear.
我们不会是首要嫌犯
We will not be the prime suspect.
好吧  那首要嫌犯是谁
Okay, well then who will be the prime suspect?
有不少  有安保人员
There's a few. We've got the security guys,
有侍者
we've got the busboys...
还有害了你的阴险小人
The shady guy who put you away.
男伴
The boyfriend.
没错  他们要找偷项链的人
Yup. They were gonna be looking for somebody.
我们只要确保不找上我们
Just had to make sure it wasn't one of us.
设计得不错
It's nice.
谢了
Thanks.
太厉害了  计划得如此精确
That is amazing! The precision...
对吧
Right?
专注于细节
It's always the attention to detail
就如同一首乐曲动听与否
and the little grace notes
关键都在几个小小的装饰音上
that really make something sing.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
我没几个闺蜜
I don't have that many close female friendships.
读书俱乐部太烂了
And book clubs are the worst.
我只是觉得
So I just thought
在这里可以分享点乐趣
this could be something fun to share.
你是因为孤独才来当罪犯吗
You're becoming a criminal because you're lonely?
谁没有个这样的时候呢  对吧
Who isn't sometimes, right?
你是独生女吗
Are you an only child?
迈阿密的《仲夏夜之梦》怎么样
Midsummer Night's Dream in Miami?
那是莎士比亚的剧
It's Shakespeare.
她在威廉斯敦演过一些夏令剧目
She did summer stock at Williamstown,
还演过一堆非百老汇的剧
plus a bunch of offBroadway.
这个怎么样  她看起来不错
What about this one? She looks good.
我看看  地方剧院
Let's see. Regional theater,
但她在茱莉亚音乐学院接受过培训
but she trained at Juilliard.
非常杰出的藏品
It's really a magnificent piece.
这是你母亲的吗
This was your mother's?
她过世后留给我的
Left to me after her passing.
一个瑞典王子用这个
A Swedish prince gave it to her
换了她的初夜
in exchange for her deflowering.
有价值吗
Are they worth something?
价值连城
Yes, they're worth quite a lot.
"拿着"  我妈妈说  "走吧"
"Take these," My mother said. "Now, go."
那晚在月光下
It was moonlight,
他说
and then he said,
"我要把星星全摘来给你"
"I'd give you every star in that sky."
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你一定很不好受
It must be difficult for you.
克劳德·贝克  是我
Claude Becker?  Yeah.
我是约翰·弗雷泽  你好
John Frazier.  Hi.
我是SPD保险公司的  你好
SPD Insurance. How are you?
克劳德
So, Claude...
跟让·克劳德·范达姆[比利时动作巨星]的名字一样
Like JeanClaude Van Damme.
对吧
Isn't it?
有何贵干
What do you want?
这是你和克卢格小姐
Here are some photographs of you
一起的照片
with Miss Kluger.
如你所见  很多照片里
Now, as you can see, there are many photographs
你的手放在她的后颈上
where your hand is on the back of her neck.
我不太记得我手放在哪里了
I don't really remember where my hands were.
像你的作风
Ah. To be you.
对吧
Right?
问题在于
Problem is,
项链被盗了
the necklace has been stolen
一条赝品取代了它的位置
and a fake has been put in its place.
眼下  最有机会
Right now, you're the person
下手的人是你
with the greatest opportunity...
我为什么要偷项链
Why would I wanna steal a necklace?
我也一直在这么问自己
That's what I keep asking myself.
这个男人
Why would this guy,
他已经什么都有了
who's got everything,
还有两个雕塑...
two of these...
为什么他会想要偷一条项链
Why would that guy wanna steal a necklace?
那你的答案是什么
What was your answer?
也许他还有东西没有
Maybe he doesn't have everything.
我觉得可以到此为止了
I think we're done here.
只是一个猜想  真的
Just a theory.  Really.
瞎猜的  到此为止吧
A shot in the dark.  We're done.
我很可能猜错了
I'm probably wrong.
这是件出色的藏品  你可以拿下
It's a beautiful piece, and I want you to have it.
价格不能再低了  能等一下吗
I can't go any lower. Just hold on one second.
你好
Hello?
Hi.
你在干什么
What're you doing right now?
你好  约翰
Hello, John.
你好  黛比
Hello, Debbie.
你气色不错  我们多久没见了
You look well, how long's it been?
好几年了  表现良好减刑了
A few years. Minus good behavior.
这样啊  对
Right.  Yeah.
谢谢你联系我  我正要打给你
Thank you for calling. I was gonna call you.
不是我干的  当然不是
Yeah, I didn't do it.  Of course not.
珠宝被盗时
You were just on camera 20 feet away
你就在摄像头旁边
while the jewels were being nicked.
纯属巧合
It's a coincidence.
不  那是有力的不在场证明
No. That's a solid alibi.
怎么回事  是你们家骨子里的基因吗
What is it? Is it genetic?
你们全家都这样吗
Are the whole family like this?
除了我的艾达阿姨
Except for my aunt Ida.
她是图书馆员吗  家庭主妇
Librarian?  Mmm. Homemaker.
好了  我就不为难你了
Right, I'm gonna make this easy for you.
我不想抓你
I don't want you.
我只想拿回项链
I just want the necklace.
不管怎么拿回来的  我就说我在出租车上捡的
I don't care. I'll say I found it in a cab.
要是只拿回一部分呢
How about some of it?
多少  假设说10%呢
How much?  Hypothetically, 10%.
那假设的其余部分呢
And where's the hypothetical rest?
我不知道  真的
Oh, I don't know. Literally.
天啊  太费劲了
Oh, God. This is exhausting!
他们要我过来的时候我就...
I mean, when they said come over, I was like... Ugh.
有时差  生物钟调不过来
You know, with the jet lag, the time difference,
这周末阿森纳要踢足总杯决赛
Arsenal in the Cup Final this weekend.
结果我在这里  真的有意思
But now I'm here. It's bloody interesting.
你看
Yeah?
这么说你不止想捞钱  还想复仇
So it's not just profit, it's revenge.
一石二鸟
It's a twofer.
他陷害你  你陷害他  扯平了
He frames you, you frame him, scores are settled.
我只是给你传信的
I'm just the courier.
世界和平  完美
All is right with the world, it's brilliant.
我只是想帮一把老朋友
Just trying to help out an old friend.
你知道吗  总有一天你得放手
You know, one day, you are gonna have to let this go?
总有一天我会的
And one day, I will.
这么说吧  我们抛开争论
Let's just say, for argument's sake,
如果我的确知道部分项链的下落
that I do know where there's a part of that necklace.
你能弄到搜查令吗
Can you get a search warrant?
我需要合理依据
I'd need probable cause.
我们也许正在着手了
Well, we may or may not be working on that right now.
你想玩个游戏吗
Do you wanna play a game?
什么游戏
What kind of game?
打牌游戏
A card game.
来吧  来吧
Yes, yes!
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
等一下
Wait.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我马上回来
I'll be right there.
你不知道钻石为何会出现在你家里
You have no idea how this came to be in your possession?
对
No.
但项链被掉包的当晚
But you were Ms. Kluger's date
你是克卢格小姐的男伴
the night these necklaces were switched.
是的
Yes, I was.
你不觉得那太过于巧合了吗
Does that strike you as a rather large coincidence?
包括一粒33.18克拉  内部完美无瑕的D级钻石...
Including a 33.18, D color, internally flawless diamond...
亚德利拍卖行年度宝石拍卖会
你听过一个叫做
Are you familiar with a company called
贝克控股的公司吗
Becker Holdings, LLC?
当然
Of course.
最近有四位
Well, it seems four sweet old ladies,
查无此人的女士
who apparently don't exist,
向贝克控股公司
have recently transferred some very large sums of money
转账了大笔资金
into Becker Holdings, LLC.
你知道是怎么回事吗  贝克先生
Do you know how that might have happened, Mr. Becker?
我要见我的律师
I think I need to talk to my lawyer.
我想也是
I think you do.
敬我们的好朋友卡尔  是克劳德
To our dear friend Carl...  Claude.
克劳德·贝克  祝他在监狱里安息
Claude Becker. May he rest in peace in prison.
干杯
Cheers.
爱你  爱你  爱你
Love you, love you, love you.
干杯  干杯
Cheers.  Cheers.
我有个问题
I have a question.
是这样的
So...
还好是他去坐牢
It's good that he went to jail,
而我们没有
'cause it's great that we didn't.
但这些首饰只卖了8500万
But if you only sold the jewels for 85 million,
那每个人要怎么才能分到1600万
how does it work out that we get 16 apiece?
你来讲吧
Do you wanna?
你以为我们只打算偷一条项链吗
You thought we were just gonna steal one necklace?
你当我们是那么没出息吗
What do you think we are, a bunch of pussies?
当时大家都急着找
See, while everyone was worried
你脖子上不翼而飞的那条项链
about what was happening around your neck...
而你正忙着把你的场子吐出来
And you were hurling your guts out...
话说回来  多谢了
Thanks for that, by the way.
你表现很好
It was amazing.
太厉害了
That was really impressive.
真的很厉害
That was really nice, actually.
晚会场地被封锁了
The place kinda went on lockdown.
厨房也清空了
The kitchen was cleared out, too.
当大家都守着门口的时候
And while everyone was watching the entrance,
我们就去展会上看了看
we thought we'd check out the exhibit.
既然能够偷到更多
Because why would you just steal one necklace,
为何只偷一条项链呢
when you could steal more?
天哪  老天
Holy shit!  Holy shit!
这可够多的
That's a lot.
是吧
Yeah.
我们不止打印了杜桑
We didn't just print the Toussaint from that thing.
还打印了很多件珠宝
We printed a lot of jewels.
感觉像是在金考快印工作
Felt like I was working at Kinko's.
与此同时
Meanwhile,
我决定去拜访一位老朋友
I decided to visit an old friend.
你好吗
亚马逊有卖这种6米长的自拍杆
Amazon sells these 20foot selfie sticks.
他们只会看到一瞬间模糊了一下
All they saw was a quick, little blur.
可以吗
可以
这是短期展览  他们还装了
It was a temporary exhibit and they built
金属架来挂列衣服
this metal grid to hang the dresses from.
一  二  三
我们就决定让小严也挂上去
We just decided to suspend Yen from that as well.
要是有人进来怎么办
What if somebody came in?
的确有人进来了
Oh. Somebody did.
抱歉  女士  你不能待在这儿
I'm sorry, ma'am, you can't be here.
我们正在清场
We're clearing this whole area.
活动组织太差了
场地里一点标牌都没有
简直疯了
疯了
我丈夫没和其他宾客在楼下
他晚上脑子会很糊涂
昨天他把鞋子放冰箱里了
他把鞋子放冰箱里了
别碰我
你们知道这裙子值多少钱吗
处理好了
We're okay.
偷项链很成功
Stealing the necklace was great,
但要是少了声东击西
but without that diversion,
要是没有清空展会现场
without clearing out the exhibit...
我们就得不到这些宝贝
We wouldn't have been able to grab these.
这些
These,
能让每个人分得3830万
which bring your cuts to $38,300,000 each.
对  太美了
Yeah, I know. It's so beautiful.
亲爱的  我知道  但是你不能把口香糖
Sweetie, I know, but you can't put gum
粘在你妹妹的头发上
in your sister's hair.
我不管她有没有先粘你的鼻子
I don't care if she tried to put it in your nose first.
看到了吗  是姐们我
What's up, YouTube? It's your girl!
看看我的新窝
Check out my new crib.
我还是业主委员会的呢
I'm on the coop board.
卡  喊卡了
Cut!  That's a cut!
卡  卡  卡  喊卡了
Cut, cut, cut!  That's a cut!
重拍一条
Resetting back to one.
镜头过来要再流畅一点
Uh, just, you know... Smoother.
请让一下  演得很好
Just a little bit of space, please. It was perfect.
情绪再快一点  再痛苦一点
I just need it faster and more damaged.
懂了吗  很好
All right? Great.
演戏有那么难吗
It's not that hard!
你在的话  会喜欢我的点子的
You would've loved it.